Guide to the Mix Collection 1970-2001 (Bulk 1987-2001) MSS 143
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- SERIES X: 1996
  - Subseries G: Media
    - Title: The Passion of Remembrance, Screened: 1987, 1996 (Box 36, Folder ID: 143.0889)
      Director: Sankofa (Attile, Martina, Blackwood, Maureen, Julien, Isaac and Marsh-Edwards, Nadine)
    - Title: Paradice, Screened: 1996 (Box 36, Folder ID: 143.0890)
      Director: Stanley, Anie "Super 8" and Chang, Patty
    - Title: Weirdo Song, Screened: 1996 (Box 37, Folder ID: 143.1202)
    - Title: [1.]--Grapefruit [2.]--Claudia [3.]--Kathy, [2.]--Screened: 1996 (Box 37, Folder ID: 143.1211)
      Director: Dougherty, Cecilia
    - Title: This Is Not An AIDS Advertisement, Screened: 1996 (Box 37, Folder ID: 143.1212)
      Director: Julien, Isaac and Sankofa
    - Title: Please Kill Me; I'm a Faggot Nigger Jew, Screened: 1996 (Box 37, Folder ID: 143.1213)
      Director: Schreiber, Rachel
    - Title: [1.]--Mireille [2.]--Sergey Kuryochin [3.]--Death of Monroe [4.]--Forest Patrol [5.]--50 Faces [6.]--New Monro [7.]--The Other Problems [8.]--24 Hours [9.]--Version [10.]--Innocent Victim [11.]--Wolfmachine, [1, 7.]--Screened: 1996 (Box 37, Folder ID: 143.1222)
      Director: Ventslova, Andrei
      Duration: [90 minutes]
    - Title: Bodily Functions, Screened: 1995 (Box 37, Folder ID: 143.1238)
    - Title: [1.]--Carmello [2.]--Mireille [3.]--Sergey Kuryochin [4.]--Death of Monroe [5.]--Forest Patrol [6.]--50 Faces [7.]--New Monro [8.]--The Other Problems [9.]--24 Hours [10.]--Version [11.]--Innocent Victim [12.]--Wolfmachine, [2, 8.]--Screened: 1996 (Box 37, Folder ID: 143.1242)
      Director: [1.]--Oertli, Christoph [2.]--Ventslova, Andrei
    - Title: Looking for Langston, Screened: 1990, 1996 (Box 37, Folder ID: 143.1460)
      Director: Julien, Isaac
    - Title: El Culebrero: la muerta de un Colombiano y el acordeonista que no esta, Screened: [1997] (Box 37, Folder ID: 143.1481)
      Director: Montoya, Patricia
    - Title: Happy Mother's Day, Screened: [1994] (Box 37, Folder ID: 143.1493)
    - Title: Puff Pieces, Screened: [1995] (Box 37, Folder ID: 143.1502)
      Director: Carmony, Karla and Amy Boyd
    - Title: Stolen Stories, Screened: Unknown (Box 37, Folder ID: 143.1511)
    - Title: Good Sister / Bad Sister, Screened:[1996] (Box 37, Folder ID: 143.1512)
      Director: Johnson, Liza
    - Title: [1.]-- Vignette [2.]-- Strani Amore [3.]-- Flor de Obsessao [4.]-- Novela Vaga [5.]-- Trip [6.]-- Jacira, Screened: [2000] (Box 37, Folder ID: 143.1553)
      Director: [2.]-- Stockler, Mari [3.]-- Rocha, Luis Antonio [4.]-- Bahia, Dora Longo [6.]-- Slinger, Ruth and Lila Rodrigues
    - Title: SIDA / AIDS, Screened: [1992] (Box 37, Folder ID: 143.1565)
      Old number: 6516 #1 PVV05
      Director: Burford, Jennifer Lou
      Duration: [120] minutes
    - Title: [1.]-- Untitled Joan [2.]-- 3 [3.]-- A Room with a View, Screened: Unknown (Box 37, Folder ID: 143.1640)
    - Title: Requiem: A Work in Progress, Screened: Unknown (Box 37, Folder ID: 143.1673)
      Director: Whiteley, Sara
      Duration: [10] minutes
    - Title: Bad Jens in My Kitchen, Screened: Unknown (Box 37, Folder ID: 143.1682)
      Director: Uhlmann, Tai
    - Title: Patty "Rocks the Blocks", Screened: [1996] (Box 37, Folder ID: 143.1694)
    - Title: Patty "Rocks the Blocks", Screened: [1996] (Box 37, Folder ID: 143.1695)
    - Title: Firefly, Screened: 1996 (Box 37, Folder ID: 143.1697)
    - Title: Splash, Screened: [1991] (Box 37, Folder ID: 143.1699)
      Old number: v12
    - Title: Kotiruokaa (Home Cooking), Screened: 1996 (Box 38, Folder ID: 143.1461)
      Director: Minkkinen, Anna
    - Title: Political Decadence, Screened: 1996 (Box 38, Folder ID: 143.1475)
    - Title: FACILE, Screened: [1996] (Box 38, Folder ID: 143.1492)
      Director: Roy, Rajendra
    - Title: One Man Show, Screened: Unknown (Box 38, Folder ID: 143.1566)
      Director: Pasolini, Antonio
    - Title: Sour Juice, Screened: [1996] (Box 38, Folder ID: 143.1570)
      Director: Oppenheim, Shoshanah
    - Title: [1.]-- Happy Mother's Day [2.]-- I Wasn't Counted at the March, Screened:[1994, 1993] (Box 38, Folder ID: 143.1572)
      Director: [1.]-- Parnes, Uzi [2.]-- Parnes, Uzi
    - Title: Stretchmark, Screened: [1996] (Box 38, Folder ID: 143.1580)
      Old number: VCTW 615-#1
    - Title: Facing AIDS: Stories of Healthcare Workers, Screened: [1993] (Box 38, Folder ID: 143.1587)
      Old number: 960004
    - Title: Merida Proscrita, Screened: Unknown (Box 38, Folder ID: 143.1590)
      Director: Ferrera-Balanquet, Raul and Enrique Novelo Cascante
    - Title: Mike's Film: Young Gay Male Survival Stories, Screened: [1996] (Box 38, Folder ID: 143.1653)
    - Title: Mike's Film, Screened: Unknown (Box 38, Folder ID: 143.1655)
    - Title: Actos Impuros, Screened: 2001 (Box 38, Folder ID: 143.1663)
      Director: Fiesco, Roberto
    - Title: Endoscope, Screened: Unknown (Box 38, Folder ID: 143.1664)
      Director: Dewhirst, Terri
    - Title: I Dream of Nicky, Screened: Unknown (Box 38, Folder ID: 143.1666)
      Director: Nguyen, Tan Hoang
    - Title: Now Pretend, Screened: Unknown (Box 38, Folder ID: 143.1700)
      Old number: v 03
    - Title: Mother's Hands, Screened: [1992] (Box 38, Folder ID: 143.1721)
      Director: Smith, Vejan
    - Title: Mix '96 Trailer: Exhibition Copy #1, Screened: 1996 (Box 39, Folder ID: 143.1525)
    - Title: Mix '96 Trailer: Exhibition Copy #2, Screened: 1996 (Box 39, Folder ID: 143.1526)
    - Title: Mix '96 Trailer, Screened: 1996 (Box 39, Folder ID: 143.1527)
    - Title: Frenzy, Screened: 1996 (Box 39, Folder ID: 143.1528)
      Director: Reiter, Jill
    - Title: I Stake My Claim, Screened: Unknown (Box 39, Folder ID: 143.1537)
      Director: Jule, Ilsa
    - Title: Internal Combustion, Screened: [1995] (Box 39, Folder ID: 143.1540)
      Director: Lebow, Alisa and Cynthia Madansky
    - Title: I, A Lamb, Screened: [1992] (Box 39, Folder ID: 143.1592)
      Director: Montgomery, Jennifer
    - Title: A Short Film About Us, Screened: Unknown (Box 39, Folder ID: 143.1595)
      Director: Smith, Rita
    - Title: The Body of a Poet: A Tribute to Audre Lorde 1934-1992, Screened: [1995] (Box 39, Folder ID: 143.1596)
      Old number: 3333 #3
    - Title: Chicken!, Screened: Unknown (Box 39, Folder ID: 143.1604)
      Director: Michelini, Tony (stinkmetal)
    - Title: Tongue in Chic, Screened: 1996 (Box 39, Folder ID: 143.1610)
      Director: Bonder, Diane and Liss Platt
    - Title: Under the Skin Game, Screened: [1996] (Box 39, Folder ID: 143.1744)
    - Title: Peckers Rising (work-in-progress), Screened: [1996] (Box 39, Folder ID: 143.1746)
      Director: Fontenot Heyd
    - Title: Metal Guru, Screened: Unknown (Box 39, Folder ID: 143.1747)
    - Title: Facile Soundtrack (Master), Screened: 1996 (Box 39, Folder ID: 143.1749)
      Performer: Fresh Fish
      Format: Audiocassette
    - Title: Apophysesia, Screened: Unknown (Box 39, Folder ID: 143.1756)
      Director: Goss, Jacqueline
      Format: 5.25" Removable Hard Disk Cartridge
      Duration: unk.
    - Title: Apophysesia, Screened: [1996] (Box 39, Folder ID: 143.1757)
    - Title: Facile, Screened: 1996 (Box 39, Folder ID: 143.1768)
      Format: 16mm film
  - Subseries H: Ticket Sales
    - Box office reports, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 931)
  - Subseries I: Outreach (see also Oversize series)
    - GLBT group contact information, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 932)
    - Imperial Kings and Queens of New York flyers, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 933)
    - Media Arts Breakfast Group, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 934)
    - Men of All Colors Together/New York, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 935)
    - Shades of Color, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 936)
    - Venus, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 938)
    - Victoria outreach, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 939)
    - The Word Is Out!, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 941)
  - Subseries J: Grants/Fundraising/Sponsorship (see also Oversize series)
    - Advertising/sponsorship - Advertising rates and work sheets, 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 942)
    - Advertising/sponsorship - Advertising register, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 943)
    - Advertising/sponsorship - Sponsorship package information, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 944)
    - Advertising/sponsorship - Magazine sponsors, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 945)
    - Advertising/sponsorship - Notes, week of Festival, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 946)
    - Advertising/sponsorship - Correspondence (STILLS INCLUDED), 1996 (Box 10, Folder 947)
    - Advertising/sponsorship - Rejected sponsors, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 948)
    - Advertising/sponsorship - HX, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 950)
    - Advertising/sponsorship - PlanetOut, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 951)
    - Advertising/sponsorship - Village Voice, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 952)
    - Grants/fundraising - Grant writing notes, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 953)
    - Grants/fundraising - Grant proposal narrative drafts, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 954)
    - Grants/fundraising - misc. grant documents, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 955)
    - Grants/fundraising - A Different Take grant proposal, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 957)
    - Grants/fundraising - Astraea, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 958)
    - Grants/fundraising - Chicago Resource Center, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 959)
    - Grants/fundraising - City of New York - Neighborhood Tourism, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 960)
    - Grants/fundraising - Department of Cultural Affairs, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 961)
    - Grants/fundraising - Experimental Television Center, Ltd., 1996 (Box 11, Folder 962)
    - Grants/fundraising - Ford Foundation, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 963)
    - Grants/fundraising - Funding Exchange, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 964)
    - Grants/fundraising - National Endowment for the Arts, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 965)
    - Grants/fundraising - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 966)
    - Grants/fundraising - New York Community Trust grant correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 967)
    - Grants/fundraising - New York Community Trust newsletter, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 968)
    - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 969)
    - Grants/fundraising - North Star Fund, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 970)
    - Grants/fundraising - Office of the Manhattan Borough President correspondence, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 968)
    - Grants/fundraising - Open Meadows correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 11, Folder 971)
    - Grants/fundraising - Playboy Foundation, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 972)
    - Grants/fundraising - Playboy Foundation, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 973)
    - Grants/fundraising - Paul Rapoport Foundation, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 974)
    - Grants/fundraising - Samuel Rubin Foundation, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 975)
    - Grants/fundraising - Stonewall Foundation, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 976)
    - Grants/fundraising - Unitarian Universalist Veatch Program, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 977)
    - Grants/fundraising - Andy Warhol Foundation for the Visual Arts, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 978)
    - Grants/fundraising - Other sources of support, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 979)
- SERIES XI: 1997
  This series contains materials pertaining to the 11th year of the Festival.
  - Subseries A: Administrative Files
    - Expenses - Budgets, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 980)
    - Expenses - Bulk mail statements, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 981)
    - Expenses - Checkbooks, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 982)
    - Expenses - Checks, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 983)
    - Expenses - Distribution, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 984)
    - Expenses - Federal Express, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 985)
    - Expenses - Fleet Bank, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 986)
    - Expenses - Invoices, bills, receipts - touring programs and misc., 1997 (Box 11, Folder 987)
    - Expenses - Invoices, bills, receipts - May-June, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 988)
    - Expenses - Invoices, bills, receipts - July-August, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 989)
    - Expenses - Invoices, bills, receipts - September-October, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 990)
    - Expenses - Invoices, bills, receipts - November-December, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 991)
    - Expenses - National Westminster Bank, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 992)
    - Expenses - Petty cash envelope, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 993)
    - Expenses - Pitney Bowes, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 994)
    - Expenses - Revenue, expenses, salaries, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 995)
    - Festival statements - Call for film/media works, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 996)
    - Festival statements - Press releases, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 997)
    - Hospitality - Festival pass information, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 998)
    - Hospitality - Press accreditation, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 999)
    - Mailing list - Address labels, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1000)
    - Mailing list - To be added, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1001)
    - Notes - Installations, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1002)
    - Notes - Minutes from Board of Directors meetings, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1003)
    - Notes - Notepad with memos, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1004)
    - Notes - Phone messages, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1005)
    - Notes - Venue scouting, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1006)
    - Organizational - Committee information, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1007)
    - Organizational - Corporate development, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1008)
    - Organizational - Internship/staff list, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1009)
    - Postal - Envelopes, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1010)
    - Postal - Postage/delivery materials, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1011)
    - Programming - Notes, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1012)
    - Programming - Party schedule, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1013)
    - Programming - Program guide, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1014)
    - Programming - Program guide - mock-up, with correspondence and invoice from designer David Pace, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1015)
    - Programming - Program listings, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1016)
    - Programming - Program listings for catalog, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1017)
    - Programming - Selection process, films listed by ranking, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1018)
  - Subseries B: Correspondence
    - Correspondence from filmmakers and film/arts organizations, A-M, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1019)
    - Correspondence from filmmakers and film/arts organizations, N-Z, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1020)
    - Correspondence from Festival re: viewing copies of works, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1021)
    - Rejection letters, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1022)
    - Artists' Space, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1023)
    - Cinema Village, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1024)
    - Downtown Arts Festival, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1025)
    - Free Speech TV, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1026)
    - Hubbard, Jim, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1027)
    - Roy, Rajendra, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1028)
    - Distribution and mailing, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1029)
    - Hospitality, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1030)
    - Interns/volunteers, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1031)
    - Press, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1032)
    - Public relations, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1033)
  - Subseries C: Entry Forms/Press Kits
    - Entry forms - Boywhore program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1034)
    - Entry forms - Closing Night featuring Tribe 8 program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1035)
    - Entry forms - Corazon: Lives of Quiet Desperation program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1036)
    - Entry forms - Cut program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1037)
    - Entry forms - De Profundis program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1038)
    - Entry forms - Dickplay program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1039)
    - Entry forms - Digitize Art! program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1040)
    - Entry forms - Documentado: Five Years of Mix Brasil program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1041)
    - Entry forms - Dollywood program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1042)
    - Entry forms - Drive program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1043)
    - Entry forms - Ethereal program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1044)
    - Entry forms - Funk program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1045)
    - Entry forms - Gong! program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1046)
    - Entry forms - I Only Have Eyes for You program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1047)
    - Entry forms - The Inconsistency of Memory program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1048)
    - Entry forms - Jack program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1049)
    - Entry forms - Lesbian Cyberspace Biography program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1050)
    - Entry forms - Melondrama program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1051)
    - Entry forms - Mixmaster program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1052)
    - Entry forms - Ooze program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1053)
    - Entry forms - Opening Night program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1054)
    - Entry forms - Platinum program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1055)
    - Entry forms - Queer(s)punk program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1056)
    - Entry forms - Raw program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1057)
    - Entry forms - Relative program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1058)
    - Entry forms - Retrovision program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1059)
    - Entry forms - Riot Grrrandmas program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1060)
    - Entry forms - Scared Stiff program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1061)
    - Entry forms - Spread program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1062)
    - Entry forms - To Catch a Glimpse program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1063)
    - Entry forms - Wig program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1064)
    - Entry forms - Guest curators' programs, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1065)
    - Entry forms - Program proposals, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1066)
    - Entry forms - Rejected entries by entry number, #1-42, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1067)
    - Entry forms - Rejected entries by entry number, #43-85, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1068)
    - Entry forms - Rejected entries by entry number, #86-129, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1069)
    - Entry forms - Rejected entries by entry number, #130-168, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1070)
    - Press kit - Shawna Dempsey and Lori Millan, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1071)
  - Subseries D: Electronic Database
    - Database (.fp3 file, 487 kb)(see archivist for access), 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1072)
  - Subseries E: Press/Promotion/Posters (see also Oversize/Mapcase series)
    - The Advocate - Mix ad, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1073)
    - HX - Mix mention in Homo Musts, Mix ad, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1074)
    - HX - Mix article in "The Reel Thing" section, mention in Homo Musts, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1075)
    - Indiewire - Ed Halter article on Mix, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1076)
    - Knitting Factory Knotes - Mix 97 schedule, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1077)
    - New York - Mix mention in Film listings, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1079)
    - New York Times - Mix mention in Film listings, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1081)
    - Simon Says - Mix mention, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1082)
    - Time Out New York - Bruce LaBruce article, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1083)
    - Time Out New York - Mix mentions in Film Alternatives + Revivals and Gay + Lesbian sections, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1084)
    - Time Out New York - Mix mentions in Film Alternatives + Revivals and Gay + Lesbian sections, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1085)
    - Mix 97 "Shoot Art" postcard, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1087)
  - Subseries F: Special Programs (see also Oversize series)
    - Bates College touring program - Correspondence, program listing, invoices, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1089)
    - Cafe con Leche - Flyers for Mix 97 benefit, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1090)
    - Latin Boys Go to Hell/Fresh Fish, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1091)
    - Mix Brasil - Pamphlets, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1092)
    - Mix Brasil - Program guide, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1093)
    - Mix Mexico - Program guide, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1095)
    - Paperveins: Prosthetic Houses installation, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1096)
    - Tribe 8 and Pansy Division - Press release and press kits, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1098)
  - Subseries G: Media
    - Title: [1.]--Callback [2.]--Too Much Lipstick, Screened: 1997 (Box 40, Folder ID: 143.0891)
      Old number: 97-001, 19252
      Director: Hunt, Sarah
    - Title: The Barry Z Story, Screened: 1997 (Box 40, Folder ID: 143.0892)
      Old number: 97-002
      Director: Kapp, Matt
      Distributor: distributed by: National Video Industries, Inc.
    - Title: In Love With Happiness, Screened: 1997 (Box 40, Folder ID: 143.0893)
      Old number: 97-004
      Director: Best, Patricia
    - Title: Heads or Tails, Screened: 1997 (Box 40, Folder ID: 143.0894)
      Old number: 97-006
      Director: Selditch, Michael
    - Title: DeAundra Peek's Mysterious Ways, Screened: 1997 (Box 40, Folder ID: 143.0895)
      Old number: 97-007
      Director: Richards, Dick
    - Title: Collette and Chantelle, Screened: 1997 (Box 40, Folder ID: 143.0896)
      Old number: 97-010
      Director: O'Keefe, Gary
    - Title: The Booby Trap, Screened: 1997 (Box 40, Folder ID: 143.0897)
      Old number: 97-011
      Director: Haug, Kate
    - Title: Pass, Screened: 1997 (Box 40, Folder ID: 143.0898)
      Old number: 97-013
    - Title: Female Bidentity: Women Telling It Like It Is, Screened: 1997 (Box 40, Folder ID: 143.0899)
      Old number: 97-014
      Director: Hardacker, Jennifer
    - Title: Vanilla Lament, Screened: 1997 (Box 40, Folder ID: 143.0900)
      Director: Crouch, Catherine
    - Title: Snow White Walk, Screened: 1997 (Box 40, Folder ID: 143.0901)
      Old number: 97-016
      Director: Hall, Elizabeth
    - Title: Outta The Blue, Screened: 1997 (Box 40, Folder ID: 143.0902)
      Old number: 97-017
      Director: Saalfield, Catherine and Hope, Melanie
    - Title: Phi-Brite, Screened: 1997 (Box 40, Folder ID: 143.0903)
      Old number: 97-018
      Director: Koone, Jeff
    - Title: Once Upon A Time For The Children, Screened: 1997 (Box 40, Folder ID: 143.0904)
      Old number: 97-019
      Director: Sloan, Tamela
    - Title: The Unveiling, Screened: 1997 (Box 40, Folder ID: 143.0905)
      Old number: 97-020, 5382 #2
      Director: Evans, Rodney
    - Title: L'abandon, Screened: 1997 (Box 40, Folder ID: 143.0906)
      Old number: 97-021
      Duration: 16 minutes
    - Title: Inflorescentia, Screened: 1997 (Box 40, Folder ID: 143.0907)
      Old number: 97-022
      Director: Gabriele, Caroline
    - Title: Monday Morning, Screened: 1997 (Box 40, Folder ID: 143.0908)
      Old number: 97-023
      Director: Henry, Kyle
    - Title: [Untitled], Screened: 1997 (Box 40, Folder ID: 143.0909)
      Old number: 97-024
    - Title: Pretty Mean, Screened: 1997 (Box 40, Folder ID: 143.0910)
      Old number: 97-025
      Director: Cline, Robin
    - Title: Heart's Desire, Screened: 1997 (Box 40, Folder ID: 143.0911)
      Old number: 97-027
      Director: Mathieu, Betsy
    - Title: Between The Lines, Screened: 1997 (Box 40, Folder ID: 143.0912)
      Old number: 97-029
      Director: Constantinou, Sophie
    - Title: [1.]--More, Bigger, Better, Faster [2.]--Astropimpin' 43 Part I The Sequel- Trailer Trash (a) [3.]--Astropimpin' 43 Part I The Sequel- Trailer Trash (b), Screened: 1997 (Box 41, Folder ID: 143.0913)
      Old number: 97-032
      Director: Jones, Bambi and Lucki Jenkins
      Distributor: distributed by: Skylark Productions
    - Title: 1919, Screened: 1997 (Box 41, Folder ID: 143.0914)
      Old number: 97-033
      Director: Gonick, Noam
    - Title: "Law of Desire" from, Clit-o-Matic: The Adventures of White Trash Girl! Episode #2, Screened: 1997 (Box 41, Folder ID: 143.0915)
      Old number: 97-034
      Director: Reeder, Jennifer
    - Title: Peep, Screened: 1997 (Box 41, Folder ID: 143.0916)
      Old number: 97-035
      Director: Rekow, Leanne
      Duration: 7 minutes
    - Title: Swing, Screened: 1997 (Box 41, Folder ID: 143.0917)
      Old number: 97-036
    - Title: Coming To Her Senses: [1.]-- Narcissus [2.]-- Tiny Bubbles [3.]-- The Pickup [4.]-- This Missing You [5.]-- Angustia [6.]-- Bright and Dark, Screened: 1997 (Box 41, Folder ID: 143.0918)
      Old number: 97-037
      Director: [1.]-- Pietrobruno, Ileana [2.]-- Myers, Bo [3.]-- McPherson, Seanna [4.]-- Daniel, Mary [5.]-- Morgado, Claudia [6.]-- Epp, Ellie
    - Title: Groove On A Stanley Knife, Screened: 1997 (Box 41, Folder ID: 143.0919)
      Old number: 97-039
      Director: Krishnan, Tinge and Beth Kotler
    - Title: Front Room, Screened: 1997 (Box 41, Folder ID: 143.0920)
      Old number: 97-041
    - Title: Put Your Hands on Your Head, Screened: 1997 (Box 41, Folder ID: 143.0921)